Only Voice Presents Episode 1
Semih's path is among the stones of Istanbul
There is a story in every step, a memory in every street
His eyes shine under the city lights
She dances with her dreams as her dreams grow
The Spirit of Istanbul is in Semih's heart
Like a dream, every moment an adventure
Minarets rise, the Bosphorus bridge is decorated with stars
Semih's song blows like the breeze of Istanbul
The streets are crowded but Semih is not alone
Light up the night with his friends
Night clubs, full of music
Semih's dance gives life to the city... [Then the music starts]
The spirit of Istanbul is in Semih's heart
Like a dream, every moment an adventure
[Music Playing] Minarets rise, the Bosphorus bridge is decorated with stars
Semih's song blows like the breeze of Istanbul
[Music Playing] Late at night, walking on the beach
[Music continues] Semih dreams of the future
[Music continues] The magic of Istanbul, always with her
[Music continues] Semih's song fills the city with love
[Music playing] The spirit of Istanbul is in Semih's heart
[Music continues] Like a dream, every moment is an adventure... [Music ends]
Only Sound Presented Episode 1 | Subtitles: Hayat Drubunu